&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：那么让我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's dive in.
我们将讨论this关键字，this关键字是可能
We're gonna talk about the this keyword, and the this keyword is maybe
所有JavaScript特性中最令人困惑的特性。
the most perpetually confused of all the JavaScript features.
我可以想象如果我们调查了这里的每个人，或者
I would imagine if we polled everyone here, or
在网上看，或者以后再看这个，你几乎可以肯定
watching online, or watching this at a later time, you've almost certainly been
在您的JavaScript职业生涯中的某个时候对这个关键字感到沮丧。
frustrated by this keyword at some point in your JavaScript career.
这是可悲的，因为它是一个非常强大的机制，而且
Which is sad because it's a very powerful mechanism, and
这也是可悲的，因为它不一定是那样的。
it's also sad because it didn't have to be that way.
这并不一定会让我们感到困惑，但是
It didn't have to be that this would be confusing to us, but
我认为很多人被this关键字搞糊涂了。
I think a lot of people got confused by the this keyword.
很简单，因为没有人告诉他们停止尝试使它像这样的关键字在
Simply because no one ever told them stop trying to make it like this keyword in
其他语言。
other languages.
所以我认为重要的是
So I think it's important for
让我们把这些东西在其他语言中的工作方式放在一边。
us to set aside how these things work in other languages.
并不是说这些都是不重要的背景，而是在某种程度上它对你有很大的帮助。
Not that those are unimportant context, but to the extent that it helps you great.
但是在某种程度上，其他一些语言的行为阻碍了您，并且
But to the extent that some other languages behavior holds you back, and
使您更难理解或利用JavaScript。
makes it so it's harder for you to understand or leverage JavaScript.
那是你应该留在门口的行李，而且
That is baggage that you should leave at the door, and
更具体地关注JavaScript是做什么的？
focus more specifically on what is JavaScript do?
原来这个关键字是
Well it turns out that this key word is
实际上比你想象的更直截了当。
actually a bit more straightforward than you would imagine.
它比你想象的更强大，而且刚刚被解释
It's more powerful than you would imagine, and it's just been explained and
教学不正确。
taught incorrectly.
所以我们会给这个话题带来一些清晰度。
So we're gonna bring some clarity to this topic.
函数的this表示或引用该调用的执行上下文。
A function's this represents or references an execution context for that call.
在其中进行调用的上下文。
A context in which that call was being made.
这完全取决于函数的调用方式。
And that is determined entirely by how the function is called.
换句话说，这个关键字赋值，如果你看一个函数
In other words, that this key word assignment, if you look at a function that
包含此关键字，则根据调用函数的方式分配该关键字。
has this keyword in it, it is assigned based upon how the function is called.
这是违反直觉的部分，因为大多数人认为你可以看看
Which is the counterintuitive part because most people think that you could look at
一个函数，并计算出这个关键字将指出什么。
a function, and figure out what this keyword is gonna point out.
但函数的定义根本无关紧要，
But the definition of the function doesn't matter at all,
确定this关键字。
to determining the this keyword.
唯一重要的是如何调用该函数？
The only thing that matters is how does that function get invoked?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果你听起来很熟悉，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If that sounds familiar to you,
这是因为我们已经讨论过灵活的可重用上下文。
it's because we've sort of already talked about a flexible reusable context.
这就是我们在谈论动态作用域时所说的，
It was what we talk about when we talk about dynamic scoping,
以及你需要我们讨论的范围。
and the scope you need of our discussion.
换句话说，这些关键字是JavaScript动态版本
So in other words, that these keyword is JavaScript's version of dynamic
范围，如果它是具有灵活的，可重用的行为的这种方式的话。
scope if it's this way of having as flexible, reusable behavior.
所以在这里我有一个函数，这个函数就是这样的，或者我很抱歉，
So here I have a function that is this aware, or I'm sorry,
我没有这样的功能。
I don't have a function that is this aware.
但你记得我有一个函数在动态作用域中
But you remember that I have a function that in a dynamic scope
动态环境感知。
dynamically context aware.
所以不是让老师去找老师，在第4行，当它引用
So instead of asking teacher to get the teacher, on line 4, when it references
老师，不是试图通过线1得到老师，而是转到线8。
teacher, instead of trying to line 1 to get teacher, it goes to line 8.
因为Ask是从第10行调用的，所以它是从另一个类作用域调用的，
Because ask was called from line 10 it was called from the other class scope,
这就是动态作用域的作用。
that's what dynamic scope does.
在JavaScript中我们有非常相似的东西，但是
And in JavaScript we have something very similar, but
它不是基于作用域边界，也不是从哪里调用的，
it's not based upon scope boundaries, or where something's called from,
它基于函数的调用方式。
it's based on how the function was called.
这就是我们最终要解决这个问题的方法。
And that's how we're gonna end up resolving it.
所以这里我有一个Ask函数的版本，它是这种感知的，
So here I have a version of the ask function which is this aware,
它使用this关键字，所以它是这个感知的。
it uses a this keyword, so it's this aware.
你会注意到我在别的地方打电话，但是
And you'll notice that I'm calling it from some other location but
那不重要。
that doesn't matter.
不是我从哪里打的，而是我怎么打的。
It's not where I call from, it's how I call it.
如果我在这里使用ask.call，我是说使用这个
If I use ask.call here, I am saying use this
特定对象作为this关键字，并在该上下文中调用函数。
particular object as your this keyword, and invoke the function in that context.
所以这个关键字在这个特殊的情况下，最终会指向我的上下文。
So this keyword in this particular case, will end up pointing at my context.
所以你可以看到这种动态的灵活性在这里发生。
So you see that sort of dynamic flexibility happening here.
你看，我可以调用同样的Ask函数，有很多不同的方式。
You see that I could call that same ask function, lots of different ways.
并为该关键字点提供许多不同的上下文对象，
And provide lots of different context objects for the this keyword point on,
这就是this关键字的动态灵活可重用性。
that's the dynamic flexible reusability of the this keyword.
这就是为什么它存在的方式，它存在如此
That's why it exists by the way, it exists so
我们可以在这些不同的上下文中调用函数。
that we can invoke functions in these different contexts.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：原来有四种不同的方式
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So it turns out that there are four different ways to
调用函数。
invoke a function.
这对你来说可能是新闻，因为你可能是
That might come as news to you, because you might be
习惯于认为函数只以一种方式调用。
used to thinking about functions as only being invoked in one way.
在JavaScript中，有四种不同的方法可以做到这一点，每种方法都是
In JavaScript there are four different ways to do so, and each one of them is
要回答的问题是，this关键字有什么不同？
gonna answer the question, what is the this keyword differently?
所以我们只需要学习这四种方法。
So we just need to learn those four ways.
这个关键字在概念上如果你能回忆起我们的讨论，
This keyword conceptually if you can recall from our discussion,
建筑的隐喻。
the metaphor of the building.
在词汇范围中，我们从当前范围开始，
In lexical scope land, we start at the current scope,
并以我们的方式向全球范围发展。
and work our way up to the global scope.
好的，在这里，我们将涉及到一个不同的建筑。
Well here we are gonna have a different building involved.
我们要开始我们的方式，我们要从建筑物的底部开始。
We're gonna start our way, we're gonna to start at the bottom of a building.
但真正的问题是，哪栋楼？
But the real question is, which building?
如果有人邀请你明天和他们一起吃午饭，他们说来
If somebody asked you to meet them for lunch tomorrow, and they said come
317号办公室见我，你自然的第一个问题是，但是什么楼？
meet me in office 317, your natural first question is gonna be, but what building?
因为在我的城市有很多办公室317。
Cause there's lots of office 317's in my city.
所以我们需要了解我们谈论的是哪个特定的背景
So we need to understand which particular context we're talking about
在我们了解如何在这种情况下寻找事物之前。
before we understand how we look for things in that context.
哪个建筑的问题是我们的this关键字规则将告诉我们什么。
And the which building question is what our this keyword rules are gonna tell us.